<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>The Star Online: Nation</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/</link>
<description>Update: Thursday, January 26, 2006 MYT 12:34:19 PM</description>
<image>
<title>The Star Online</title>
<url>http://localhost/news/images/404.jpg</url>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/</link>
<width>88</width>
<height>31</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Court of Appeal to hear contempt arguments over Metramac case</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/20060126122711&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Metramac Corporation Sdn Bhd&#8217;s lawyer Datuk Muhammad Shafee Abdullah has been taken to task by the Court of Appeal over a complaint letter against one of the judges, Justice Gopal Sri Ram.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lawyer, manager plead not guilty</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219770&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A lawyer and her administrative manager pleaded not guilty to committing criminal breach of trust (CBT) of RM3mil belonging to Maju Holdings Sdn Bhd.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>PTPTN to give out loans only for accredited courses</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13220131&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Beware when signing up for a course at private education institutions &#8211; from July 1, the National Higher Education Fund Corporation (PTPTN) will only give out loans for accredited courses.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Smugglers mailing drugs into the country</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219785&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Drug smugglers are now mailing drugs into the country as their attempts to get individuals to bring in the substance from overseas are being foiled by the authorities.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Five-day week for banks</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13221860&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Banks will implement a five-day working week from Feb 1 in a bid to encourage electronic banking and give bank employees more time off.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Najem now pledges RM1m to KL Hospital</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219973&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Self-proclaimed billionaire Elie Youssef Najem has now pledged RM1mil to the Kuala Lumpur Hospital.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Imagine a fish the size of a mosquito</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13218956&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Scientists said they had discovered the world&#8217;s tiniest fish &#8211; a species that lives in peat wetlands in South-East Asia and, when fully grown, is the size of a large mosquito.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Penang&#8217;s very own Twin Towers</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13207181&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The View&#8217;s selling point may be its namesake but The View is a spectacle itself due to its strong resemblance to the Petronas Twin Towers in Kuala Lumpur.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fireworks explode while being disposed of</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13223060&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Millions of ringgit worth of confiscated fireworks exploded while they were being disposed of at the Hobart Army Camp in Jeniang, some 30km from here.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pick right people for IPCMC</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13220493&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Public belief and confidence in the proposed Independent Police Complaints and Misconduct Commission (IPCMC) will hinge strongly on the selection of its members and its powers and functions.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sex pills among smuggled items seized</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13222696&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Twenty-one boxes of sex stimulation pills were among RM16,115 worth of smuggled goods seized by the Kedah Anti-Smuggling Unit (UPP) in an operation here.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fishing boats delivered to Kedah at last</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219968&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Fifty-seven fishing boats built for Kedah fishermen but left exposed to the elements in Sabak Bernam, Selangor, and Hutan Melintang, Perak, have finally arrived in Kedah.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Black Metal not linked to satanism, say its fans</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13208028&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Black Metal, like any other type of music, is only a genre, said Joseph Prabagar, founder and director of record label Demonzend.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pomelo is a must-have,but rainy weather has slowed ripening process</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13089557&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The rainy weather has slowed the ripening of pomeloes here, creating an even higher demand for the auspicious fruit during the Chinese New Year period.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Reunion dinner a way of bonding families</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13036135&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>It is always nice to get together with loved ones but for the Chinese, the most special family gathering has to be the reunion dinner on the eve of Chinese New Year.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Good tidings via fresh blooms</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13208255&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Good tidings come in a package, and brightly coloured fresh flowers remain the best way to convey this during the Chinese New Year.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Police to step up enforcement during CNY</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13220162&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A friendly mahjong game among relatives is permissible but nothing more than two tables.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>No reunion joy for some convicts</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13218241&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Ah Mei (not her real name) always looks forward to the reunion dinner on Chinese New Year&#8217;s eve but she has missed this significant gathering for the past three years.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mum gets her CNY wish</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13217552&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A single mother is set to get her wish for the Year of the Dog &#8211; to give her children an education.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Najib inspired by dad</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13225302&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>It did not cross Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak's mind to be actively involved in politics one day although he was a student leader during his university days in England.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Singapore names orchid after the King</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13218654&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A fast-growing terrestrial hybrid orchid from the Spathoglottis species was named &#8220;Spathoglottis Syed Sirajuddin&#8221; in conjunction with the visit by the Yang di-Pertuan Agong Tuanku Syed Sirajuddin Syed Putra Jamalullail to Singapore&#8217;s National Orchid Garden.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>RM6,000 for alligator fish</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/20060126081756&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The farmer who
caught the alligator gar fish last
week has sold his catch to a
businessman from Kuala Lumpur
for RM6,000.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Man apologises for wife&#8217;s assault on discipline teacher</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/20060126082017&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A former Jit Sin High School student broke
down as he hugged several teachers to seek forgiveness on behalf of his wife, who had
allegedly attacked a teacher with a pair of scissors.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unusual find has villagers all excited</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13224525&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The usually calm and quiet village of Kampung Pengkalan Sungai Udang in Teluk Gong near here has been enveloped in excitement in recent days over an unusual find.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Transformer thieves held</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13220887&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A syndicate, believed to be experienced in stealing power transformers from sub-stations, has been busted with the arrest of four men.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>RM2.5b in Visa card transactions</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13224294&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Malaysians spent RM2.48bil on&lt;I&gt; &lt;/I&gt;their Visa cards during the holiday season from Nov 17 to Dec 31, last year &#8211; up by 17% from the corresponding period last year, according to Visa Asia Pacific.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>All work and no play makes Fasha a special star</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13218829&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Fasha Sandha describes herself as a workaholic. The fresh-faced actress admits being hardworking and needing little beauty sleep.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Umno man suspended from party post</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13223108&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Kubang Kerian Umno division head Mohd Fauzi Ismail, charged with two counts of money laundering on Sunday, has been suspended from his party post.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>&#8216;Lecturers &#8216;face new &#8216;hurdle&#8217; to &#8216;promotion</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13206317&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>University lecturers hoping to be promoted will now have to clear an extra hurdle.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Industrial training for school dropouts without SPM</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13220584&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>School dropouts without Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia will be allowed to attend certain courses at the 21 government-run industrial training colleges.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>MB determined to protect big trees</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219994&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The felling of a century-old &lt;I&gt;tualang&lt;/I&gt; tree near Taiping has sounded the alarm bells for the Terengganu government.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sarawak using &#8216;fish test&#8217; to check if rivers are clean</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13218263&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Sarawak has come up with guidelines for &#8220;fish indicators&#8221; &#8211; the first in the country &#8211; as a method to gauge the cleanliness of rivers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Malaysians help raise airfare for 15 Chinese</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219854&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Fifteen Chinese fishermen will get to spend Chinese New Year with their families in Hainan, China.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Swiss Alps scene shot in Genting Highlands</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13210692&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Genting Highlands has become the substitute setting for Switzerland in the Malaysian-made Tamil movie &lt;I&gt;Ethirkaalam&lt;/I&gt; (The Future) which will be released in Malaysia and Singapore next month.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rise in accident claims</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13217871&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Insurance companies paid out a whopping RM1.602bil in road accident claims in the first nine months of last year &#8211; 4% more than the RM1.542bil disbursed in the corresponding period in 2004.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Customs D-G gets threats via SMS</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13223528&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Having spent the better part of his career doing preventive work in the Customs Department, receiving threats is not something new for its director-general Datuk Abdul Rahman Abdul Hamid.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Police to get 400 more patrol cars</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219203&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The public can expect more efficient patrolling and crime prevention from the police as the force is getting an additional 400 mobile patrol vehicles this year.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>NS camp operator RM900,000 in arrears</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219695&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The operator of a national service (NS) training camp in Rompin has come under fire from the state government for purportedly defaulting on payments to 28 suppliers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Residents fear repeat mudslides</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13225557&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Impending quarry operations at Gunung Jerai have raised concerns of mudslides among nearby residents. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Defaulters&#8217; kids barred</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13225569&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The offer for entry into Form 1 and 4 to Mara Junior Science Colleges (MRSM) will automatically become void if the parents or guardians of students are on Mara&#8217;s blacklist or facing legal action for failing to repay loans given by the agency.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Quit rent for some areas in Negri to rise by 200%</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13220100&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Quit rent for certain areas in Negri Sembilan is set to increase this year by as much as 200% following the reclassification of land use.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Keeping watch on endangered rhinos</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219063&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>The WWF together with the Sabah Wildlife Department and the Sabah Foundation, plan to set up a monitoring and survey team to gather information on rhinos in the state.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Girl, 15, held for drug trafficking</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13219053&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>Three men and an underage girl, believed to be members of a drug trafficking syndicate, were arrested when a police team raided a house near Taman Temiang here about 6am on Tuesday.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rep reports threats by in-laws</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13222903&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description>A state assemblyman lodged a police report on Tuesday claiming that his in-laws had threatened him over a family dispute.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 minutes news</title>
<link>http://thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2006/1/26/nation/13217927&amp;sec=nation</link>
<description></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>

